Ctrl... Alt... Defeat
Virtually Heroes is a fantasy, action, science
fiction film directed by G.J. Echternkamp.
Two self-aware characters in a "Call of Duty" style video game
struggle with their screwy, frustrating existence.
Books, played by Robert Baker.
Nova, played by Brent Chase.
Jennifer, played by Katie Savoy.
Monk, played by Mark Hamill.
Merk, played by Ben Messmer.
General Tran, played by Kevin Trang.
Virtually Heroes is a 2013 American low-budget gamer film directed by G.J.
Echternkamp and starring Robert Baker and Mark Hamill.
Produced by Roger Corman, it made its world premiere
at the 2013 Sundance Film Festival.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.